http://pagparts.com/privacy.php

My Account | Cart Contents | Checkout
Categories
Braking->Drivetrain->Engine Parts->Eurodyne Software->Exhaust->Fueling->Hardware->Intercoolers->Silicone/Rubber->Turbo Gauges / Controllers->Turbo Kits->Turbo ManifoldsWater/Meth Injection KitsTurbochargers->Wastegates / DV's /BOV's->
Manufacturers
Please SelectACL PerformanceAEMAeromotiveAeroquipARPAutotechBilsteinBorg WarnerBoschBremboBrute Connectin..Bullseye PowerCat CamsClutchmastersClutchnetCP PistonsDelphiDevils OwnEurodyneEurospecGarrettH&RInnovate Motors..JE PistonsJE PistonsKing BearingsKoniOEMPauterPeloquinsPPTPrecision Turbo..RacewareRussell Perform..SEM MotorsportsSiemens DekaSouthbend Clutc..Spec ClutchSupertech Perfo..TiALTurbosmartWalbroWavetracWiseco Pistons
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Information
Shipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseContact Us
$slideshow
Privacy Notice
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Pag Parts website. On some pages, you can order products. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in the "My Account" area. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error, or by changing your information in the "My Account" area.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (347) 561-4802 or send us an email at sales@pagparts.com.
Shopping Cart
0 items
Copyright © 2020 PAG PARTSPowered by Pag Parts ::
Pag Parts
